(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
1周年記念LIVE 僕が主役でもいいですか？ - Amane Kanata 1st Anniversary LIVE -
1st Anniversary LIVE: May I Be the Main Character? - Amane Kanata 1st Anniversary LIVE -
“May I be a star today?”
FROM 2019/12/27 passed 39 days
she has descended in the winter and has been good at using powerpoint
FROM 2019/12/27 passed 163 days
passed monetization examination of webcasting site.
FROM 2019/12/27 passed 208 days
I started to live with the dragon and comet.
FROM 2019/12/27 passed 366 days
appeared in “hololive 2nd fes. Beyond the Stage” held on the other day, and now...
天音かなた 1st Anniversary LIVE
Amane Kanata 1st Anniversary LIVE
Let's get started.
お待たせしましたー！
I've kept you waiting!
1周年記念、天音かなた、よろしくねー！
My 1st anniversary, I'm Amane Kanata! Best regards!
どうだっていい言を　嘘って吐いて戻れない
Words that don't matter, I spat them out as lies and can't go back
時効なんてやってこない　奪ったように奪われて
The statute of limitations will never come, being robbed just as I robbed others
今日だって叶わない　思ったように騙せない
Even today, it won't come true, I can't deceive as I intended
腐っている僕には　腐ったものがわからない
For someone as rotten as me, I can't tell what's rotten anymore
おいで　ココまで
Come here, this far
成れ！！
Become!!
隠して仕舞ったんだ
I ended up hiding it all away
メーデー僕と判っても
Mayday, even if you realize it's me
抱き締めなくていいんだよ
You don't have to hold me tight
メーデー僕が解ったら
Mayday, if you understand me
もう一度嘲笑ってくれるかな
I wonder if you'll laugh at me once more
Wow Wow Wow...
魔物だって知るんだよ
Knowing that I'm just a monster
Wow Wow Wow...
嘘つきだって知るんだよ
Knowing that I'm just a liar
ねえ
Hey
戻ったはずが　キョドってYESを声に出す
I thought I'd returned, but I awkwardly shout 'YES' aloud
後悔の脆弱は　騙したほうが正義なの
The fragility of regret, is it justice to be the one who deceives?
卑怯だって構わない　祈っておいてそれはない
I don't care if I'm a coward, I prayed for it, but it's not like that
飾っていた饒舌が　墓穴を掘って焼ける様
The eloquence I'd been flaunting, is like digging my own grave and burning
負い目　どこまで
Debt, how much further?
灰色！！
Gray!!
被害者ヅラしたんだ
I played the victim
メーデー僕を叱ってよ
Mayday, please scold me
正直者が夢見たなら
If an honest person were to dream
メーデー僕を裁いてよ
Mayday, please judge me
最後まで甘えてしまうのは
Indulging myself until the very end is...
Wow Wow Wow...
幽霊だって知るんだよ
Knowing that I'm just a ghost
Wow Wow Wow...
空白だって知るんだよ
Knowing that I'm just a void
ねえ
Hey
足りないものを望んだら　僕じゃない僕に出会ったよ
If I wish for what I lack, I encountered a 'me' that wasn't me
それでも前に進んだの　クラクラしちゃう夜も
Even so, I moved forward, even through dizzying nights
育てたの　君には僕が見えるか
I raised it. Can you see me?
孤独なピエロが
A lonely clown...
メーデー　僕と判っても　もう抱き締めなくていいんだよ
Mayday, even if you know it's me, you don't have to hold me anymore.
メーデー　僕が解ったら
Mayday, if you understand me...
もう一度　嘲笑ってくれるかな
Will you sneer at me once more?
メーデー　僕を叱ってよ　正直者が夢見たいなら
Mayday, scold me; if an honest person wants to dream...
メーデー　僕を裁いてよ　最後まで甘えてしまうのは
Mayday, judge me; depending on you until the very end is...
メーデー　僕を暴いてよ　もう直終わるこの世界から
Mayday, expose me; from this world that's about to end...
メーデー　僕と踊ってよ　最初からイナイと理解してた？
Mayday, dance with me; did you know I wasn't here from the start?
Wow... 嘘憑きだって知るんだよ
Wow... I'll find out you're a liar.
Wow... 亡霊だって知るんだよ
Wow... I'll find out you're a ghost.
Wow... 空白だって知るんだよ
Wow... I'll find out it's a void.
どうだっていい言を　嘘って吐いて戻れない
Spitting out trivial words as lies, I can't go back.
時効なんてやってこない　奪ったように奪われて
A statute of limitations will never come; I'm robbed just as I robbed.
沈むように溶けてゆくように
As if sinking, as if melting away.
二人だけの空が広がる夜に
Into the night where a sky for just the two of us unfolds.
「さよなら」だけだった
It was only a "goodbye."
その一言で全てが分かった
With that single word, I understood everything.
陽が沈み出した空と君の姿
The sky where the sun had begun to set and your silhouette...
フェンス越しに重なっていた
...were overlapping through the fence.
初めて会った日から
From the day we first met,
僕の心の全てを奪った
you stole every part of my heart.
どこか儚い空気を纏う君は
You, shrouded in a somewhat fleeting atmosphere,
寂しい目をしてたんだ
had such lonely eyes.
いつだってチックタックと鳴る世界で
In a world that's always ticking away,
何度だってさ
time and time again,
触れる心ない言葉うるさい声に
even if heartless words and noisy voices touch me,
涙が零れそうでも
and tears are about to fall,
ありきたりな喜び
ordinary happiness is something
きっと二人なら見つけられる
I'm sure the two of us can find.
騒がしい日々に笑えない君に
To you, who can't smile in these noisy days,
思い付く限り眩しい明日を
I'll give as dazzling a tomorrow as I can imagine.
明けない夜に落ちてゆく前に
Before we fall into a night that never ends,
僕の手を掴んでほら
come on, take my hand.
忘れてしまいたくて閉じ込めた日々も
Even the days I locked away, wanting to forget them,
抱きしめた温もりで溶かすから
I'll melt them away with the warmth of my embrace.
怖くないよいつか日が昇るまで
Don't be afraid; until the sun rises someday,
二人でいよう
let's stay together.
君にしか見えない
I hate the way you look
何かを見つめる君が嫌いだ
at something only you can see.
見惚れているかのような
As if you're entranced,
恋するような
as if you're in love...
そんな顔が嫌いだ
I hate that look on your face.
信じていたいけど信じれないこと
Things I want to believe but can't,
そんなのどうしたってきっと
no matter what, I'm sure
これからだっていくつもあって
there will be many of those from now on,
そのたんび怒って泣いていくの
and each time, we'll get angry and cry.
それでもきっといつかはきっと
Even so, surely someday, surely we
僕らはきっと
will surely
分かり合えるさ信じてるよ
understand each other; I believe it.
「もう嫌だ」って疲れたんだって
"I'm sick of this," "I'm tired," you say,
がむしゃらに差し伸べた
shaking off my hand
僕の手を振り払う君
that I reached out so frantically.
「もう嫌だ」って疲れたよなんて
"I'm sick of this," "I'm tired,"
本当は僕も言いたいんだ
truth is, I want to say those words too.
ほらまたチックタックと鳴る世界で
Look, in this world ticking away again,
何度だってさ
time after time,
君のために用意した言葉
none of the words I prepared for you
どれも届かない
seem to reach you.
「終わりにしたい」だなんてさ
When I got swept up and said,
釣られて言葉にした時
"I want to end this,"
君は初めて笑った
you smiled for the very first time.
騒がしい日々に笑えなくなっていた
In these noisy days where I'd forgotten how to smile,
僕の目に映る君は綺麗だ
you, reflected in my eyes, are beautiful.
明けない夜に溢れた涙も
Even the tears shed in the never-ending night
君の笑顔に溶けていく
melt away into your smile.
変わらない日々に泣いていた僕を
I, who was crying in these unchanging days,
君は優しく終わりへと誘う
you gently invite me toward the end.
沈むように溶けてゆくように
As if sinking, as if melting away,
染み付いた霧が晴れる
the deep-seated mist clears.
君が跳ねる
You bounce
眩しいほどに
So bright
美しくて
And beautiful
閉じ込めてしまいたくて
I wanted to lock you away
秘密の場所に
In a secret place
差し伸べてくれた
The hand you reached out
君の手を取る
I take it
涼しい風が
A cool breeze
空を泳ぐように今
As if swimming through the sky
吹き抜けていく
Blows through right now
繋いだ手を離さないでよ
Don't let go of my hand
二人今、夜に駆け出していく
The two of us are running into the night now
秒針を噛む
作詞 ACAね / 作曲 ぬゆり、ACAね
Byoushin wo Kamu
Lyrics: ACAne / Composition: nulut, ACAne
退屈な希望
Boring hope
いつも通り通り過ぎた
Passed by as usual
一回とわかった 戻らない
I understood once, it's not coming back
確信犯でしょ？
You're a convinced criminal, right?
夕食中に泣いた後
After crying during dinner
君は笑ってた
You were laughing
私もそうだよ
Saying, "me too,"
って 偽りの気持ち被せて
Covering it with fake feelings
吐いて黙って
Spitting it out, keeping silent
ずっと黙って
Forever keeping silent
何が何でも
No matter what
面と向かって「さよなら」
Saying "goodbye" to your face
する資格もないまま
Without even the right to do so
僕は
I am...
灰に潜り 秒針を噛み
Diving into the ash, biting the second hand
白昼夢の中でガンガン砕いた
Crushing it away in a daydream
でも壊れない
But it won't break
止まってくれない
It won't stop for me
本当は知らないまま進むのさ
Advancing while not really knowing the truth
このまま奪って 隠して 忘れたい
I want to steal it away, hide it, and forget like this
分かり合うまるひとつもなくても
Even if there's not a single point we understand
会って「ごめん」って返さないでね
Don't meet me and say "sorry" in return
形のない言葉はいらないから
Because I don't need formless words
気安い一生
An easy life
何でも受け止めると言ったきり
Ever since saying I'd accept anything
何も変えることはない
There's nothing to change
誰でも
Anyone
僕の代わりじゃなくても 君に守られた
Even if it wasn't my replacement, I was protected by you
目も口も
Eyes and mouth
意味がないほどに
To the point of being meaningless
塞ぎ込んで
Sinking into silence
動けない僕を
I, who cannot move
見つけないで
Don't find me
ほっといてくんないか
Won't you leave me alone?
どこ見ても どこにいても 終わらない
No matter where I look or where I am, it doesn't end
灰に潜り 秒針を噛み
Diving into the ash, biting the second hand
白昼夢の中でガンガン砕いた
Crushing it away in a daydream
でも壊れない
But it won't break
止まってくれない
It won't stop for me
演じ続けるのなんだ？
What is it that I keep performing?
このまま奪って 隠して 忘れたい
I want to steal it away, hide it, and forget like this
分かり合うまるひとつもなくても
Even if there's not a single point we understand
会って「ごめん」って返さないでね
Don't meet me and say "sorry" in return
形のない言葉はいらないから
Because I don't need formless words
姿叫んで
Screaming the figure
明日は来ない
Tomorrow won't come
嘲笑うなら情けない
If you mock me, it's pathetic
誰のせいでもないこと
Something that's nobody's fault
あら探しのせいにしたくて
I wanted to blame it on fault-finding
化けているのかな
Am I pretending?
本当は分かってるんだ
I actually know the truth
見放されても 信じてしまうよ
Even if I'm abandoned, I end up believing
このまま奪って 隠して 忘れたい
I want to steal it away, hide it, and forget like this
このまま奪って 隠して 放したい
I want to steal it away, hide it, and let go
分かり合うまるひとつもなくても
Even if there's not a single point we understand
会って「ごめん」って返さないでね
Don't meet me and say "sorry" in return
形のない
As ourselves
僕らして
Without form
そこは消えない
That won't disappear
嘘はいらないから
Because I don't need lies
Lai-Lai...
KING
作詞・作曲：Kanaria
Lyrics & Music: Kanaria
ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi!
幽閉利口逝く前に
Before confined cleverness passes away
幽閉利口に難儀だい
It's a struggle for confined cleverness
幽閉ストップ 知ってないし
I don't know anything about a confined stop
勘弁にしといてなんて惨憺
Saying 'give me a break' is so wretched
ひたひたと降る欠片のアイロニー
The irony of fragments falling steadily
誰もが願う無機質なような
Like the inorganic state everyone wishes for
一足先に始めて太陽な
Starting a step ahead, like the sun
先が見えないバンジーハッピーショー
A bungee happy show where you can't see ahead
無いのあなたにお願い一つ
I have one request for you who has nothing
相も変わらずおまけにワーニワーニ
As usual, and furthermore, worry worry
無いのあなたにお願い一つ
I have one request for you who has nothing
張り詰めた思い込め
Putting all my pent-up feelings into it
Left Side, Right Side
歯を剥き出して パッパッパッ
Baring your teeth, pa pa pa
照れくさいね
How embarrassing
Left Side, Right Side
歯を剥き出して パッパッパッ
Baring your teeth, pa pa pa
You are KING
無邪気に遊ぶ 期待期待のダーリンダーリン
Playing innocently, my expected darling darling
健気に笑う 痛い痛いの消える
Smiling bravely, the pain, pain, goes away
無様に死ねる 苦い思いも無くなって
I can die unsightly, with all bitter thoughts gone
ラララブラットタッタ
La la Love Rat-ta-ta
嫌い嫌いの最低泣いてら
Hate, hate, I'm crying at my worst
無いのあなたにお願い一つ
I have one request for you who has nothing
相も変わらず自虐のワーニワーニ
As usual, self-deprecating worry worry
無いのあなたにお願い一つ
I have one request for you who has nothing
張り詰めた思い込め
Putting all my pent-up feelings into it
Left Side, Right Side
歯を剥き出して パッパッパッ
Baring your teeth, pa pa pa
邪魔くさいね
How bothersome
Left Side, Right Side
歯を剥き出して パッパッパッ
Baring your teeth, pa pa pa
You are KING
みんな、ありがとう
Thank you everyone!
ということで、ゲストに来てくれました
So, joining me as guests...
同期の常闇トワと、桐生ココです！
...are my fellow 4th gen members, Tokoyami Towa and Kiryu Coco!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
初めてね、3人で踊りましたけど
It was our first time performing as a trio...
めっちゃ楽しかった！
...and it was so much fun!
最高！
The best!
わちゃわちゃ感が4期生っぽかったな
That chaotic energy was so typical of the 4th gen.
みんなびっくりしたんじゃないかな、この二人が来てくれるって
I bet everyone was surprised to see these two show up.
やめなさい、うるさい、うるさい
Stop it! You're being too loud!
4期生はね、やっぱり4期生はね
As for the 4th generation... as expected...
よいしょ、全員ね
Alright, everyone...
トワもね、ルーナも明日、明後日かな
Towa, and Luna tomorrow or the day after...
1周年を迎えますので
...will be celebrating our 1st anniversary.
そうですよ
That's right!
これからも4期生頑張っていきたいと思いますので
We'll keep doing our best as the 4th generation...
皆さん、応援よろしくお願いします！
...so please keep supporting us!
ありがとう
Thank you!
よし、今度はみんなで歌おうな
Alright, let's all sing together next time.
歌おう
Let's do it!
今度は4期みんなで
Next time, with all of the 4th gen.
とりあえず2021年初めて
Anyway, for the first time in 2021...
最初に歌った歌、これだったんだよ、ほら、4期生の
...this was the first song we sang. It's the 4th gen's...
歌い始め
...first song of the year!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
あけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year!
やったよ、本当におめでたいね
We did it! It's really worth celebrating.
1年早かった
The year went by so fast.
また今年も頑張りたいと思います、な
I want to work hard again this year, right?
もう、4期生、みんなで楽しく頑張ります！
Yeah, the 4th gen will all work hard and have fun together!
頑張ろう、ありがとう
Let's do it! Thank you.
トワとココとはちょっと名残惜しいけど、ありがとう
It's a shame to say goodbye to Towa and Coco already, but thank you.
かなたのステージだからね
It's your stage, after all.
あなたの主役、主役
You're the star! The star!
ありがとう、バイバイ
Thank you! Bye-bye!
ポーズ取っておこうよ、バイバイ！
Let's strike a pose before we go. Bye-bye!
はい、ということでゲストでトワとココが来てくれました
Alright, so Towa and Coco joined us as guests.
いや本当、本当に嬉しい
I'm really, really happy.
この間のね、あの延期になっちゃった日も
Even on the day it was postponed...
二人はね、来てくれて、一緒に練習をね、してくれました
...the two of them came and practiced with me.
本当に本当に、同期のみんな
Truly, all my gen-mates...
今日はね、あの、一緒には歌えなかったけど
I couldn't sing with them today, but...
わためとルーナも
...Watame and Luna too...
かけがえのない、一生、大切...
...are irreplaceable, lifelong treasures...
よろしくお願いします。
Thank you very much.
それでは次の曲、まいります！
Now, here is the next song!
よし、それではステージ、ちょっと移動しちゃおうかな。
Alright, I think I'll move to the other stage now.
えっ、えい！
Eh, e-i!
あ、来た来た来た来た。
Oh, I'm here, I'm here.
それではこちらにて歌わせていただきたいと思います。
Now, I'd like to sing for you here.
本日、えっと、22時ですね、
Today, at 10:00 PM,
この後、この配信の終わった後、22時15分に投稿されます...
Right after this stream ends, at 10:15 PM, it will be posted...
歌ってみたで歌わせていただきました、アウトサイダー、
The song 'Outsider' that I covered for my cover video,
歌いたいと思います。
I'm going to sing it now.
アウトサイダー
Outsider
ねぇねぇ この世界をどっかからひっくり返したくて
Hey, hey, I want to turn this world upside down from somewhere
正義感なんてありもしない
There's no such thing as a sense of justice
まあまあそんなんで 少年少女歌いまして
Well, well, with that, boys and girls are singing
唸り始めた快進撃さ
The breakthrough has started to roar
低体裁で 人体で 傲慢な
Low profile, human body, arrogant
最下等で最高な相棒さ
The lowest and greatest partner
単純明快な考えが
A simple and clear thought
僕をここで覚醒させちゃいないか
Isn't it awakening me here?
今この身を以て 重石を剥いで
Now, with this body, peeling off the weights
君にだけにしかできないことは何だ
What is it that only you can do?
そこにいないで 慰めなんていらないよ
Don't stay there, I don't need any comfort
荒地になってしまわぬように
So that it doesn't become a wasteland
その名を隠して ここに現れたのさ
Hiding that name, I appeared here
腐ってる奴らを 探って蹴って笑って這いて
Searching for the rotten ones, kicking them, laughing, and crawling
現状 縋って
Clinging to the current situation
将来ない 勝手にやってな
There's no future, just do what you want
もう配って 否定したって 銘したって 誰かのせいにしたって
Already distributed, even if denied, even if named, even if blamed on someone else
フラッシュバックして 初心者の言い訳して
Flashing back, making excuses like a beginner
感情も根も腐ってしまいました
Emotions and roots have both rotted away
思い出したくない一日は
The day I don't want to remember
ここに吐き出してしまいなよ
Just spit it out right here
要らんもんだけ捨て去って
Just throw away only the unnecessary things
僕をここで壊しちゃいないか
Isn't it breaking me here?
今はこれを持って 口を噤んで
Now, hold this and shut your mouth
染み付いて夜の傷が癒えないのなら
If the deep-seated wounds of the night won't heal
涙は見せないで こんな恥なんていらないよ
Don't show tears, I don't need such shame
全て失ってしまわぬように
So that everything isn't lost
変わらぬものがここにあるとするならば
If there is something unchanging here
夜が明ける前に そう咲いてしまえと
Before the dawn breaks, bloom just like that
白と黒の色のない世界に溢れた
Overflowing in a world without white and black colors
愛も全部ないよ その世界に塗れた
There is no love at all, smeared in that world
心の庭 決して許してはくれないから
Because the garden of the heart will never forgive me
影は伸びきって 日は落ち切って
The shadows have fully stretched, the sun has fully set
明日を迎えることが許されたなら
If I were allowed to welcome tomorrow
救われてたかな それでも僕は
Would I have been saved? Even so, I...
今この身を以て 重石を剥いで
Now, with this body, peeling off the weights
君にだけにしかできないことは何だ
What is it that only you can do?
そこにいないで 慰めなんていらないよ
Don't stay there, I don't need any comfort
荒地になってしまわぬように
So that it doesn't become a wasteland
その名を隠して ここに現れたのさ
Hiding that name, I appeared here
腐ってる奴らを 探って蹴って笑って這いて
Searching for the rotten ones, kicking them, laughing, and crawling
その小さな勇気が 僕の胸を焦がすから
Because that small courage scorches my chest
フィクサー
Fixer
今日までの記憶の全部を消してしまう時まで眠れない
I can't sleep until the moment I erase all my memories up to today
あしたを歩いていく自分の苦が欲しくてたまらない
I can't help but crave the bitterness of myself walking into tomorrow
「大丈夫」と言わせて あとから君のせいにさせてはくれないか
Let me say "it's okay", and later let me blame it on you
今更意味ないから あとから君のせいにさせてはくれないか
It's meaningless now, so later let me blame it on you
できやしない約束を 滔々と溢れる一言一言ばかり
Endlessly overflowing word by word of promises that can't be kept
もう奪われるくらい
Being snatched away so much
意味をなさない 何もできない
Making no sense, unable to do anything
見えない 逃げたい 飛びたい やめたい そらさないから
I can't see, I want to run, I want to fly, I want to stop, I won't look away
沈め 沈め 這い上がれないほどまで
Sink, sink, until you can't climb back up
飽きるまで 落とせ 落とせ
Until you're bored, drop, drop
救い垂らす時まで
Until the time of salvation drips
嘘つく粒をのどからしぼり出して日々ごと噛みくだく
Squeezing out the seeds of lies from my throat and crushing them day by day
下手な花火でしたような口ぶりにそってやり過ごす
Getting by following the way of speaking like poor fireworks
なりたくはなかった 共役なはずの眠い眠い理想で
I didn't want to become that, with a sleepy, sleepy ideal that should be conjugate
救われることを待つ
Waiting to be saved
一番目は胃の口だよ
The first is the entrance to the stomach
ちから強くかたく痛く噛みしめて
Biting down strongly, firmly, and painfully
死んでしまえ 死んでしまえ
Die, die
この先も過去も知らず
Knowing neither the future nor the past
壊せ 壊せ
Break, break
どうせなら加害者になればいい
If anything, you should just become the perpetrator
堪えきれない苛立ちも
The unbearable irritation too
何も生まない悲しみも
And the sadness that produces nothing
味気なくて吐き出す前に
Before spitting out the tastelessness
もう、もう次を歌え
Already, already sing the next
沈め 沈め
Sink, sink
壊せ 壊せ
Break, break
踊れ 踊れ 灰色になりきる前に
Dance, dance, before becoming completely gray
打ち鳴らせ
Strike and sound
変われ 変われ 眠りに落ちる時まで
Change, change, until the moment you fall asleep
奪え 奪え
Snatch, snatch
飼いならした嘘あばいて
Expose the tamed lies
見えてあげる 頭に起きた
I'll show you, what happened in my head
虚像を見ていた
I was looking at a virtual image
アディショナルメモリー / 作詞・作曲：じん
Additional Memory / Lyrics & Composition: Jin
浮かんで 転げ落ちて 出会ったエンドロール
Floating, tumbling down, meeting the end roll
歪んで 変わり果てた 未来の走馬灯
Distorted, completely changed lantern of the future
おしまいな 幕の切れてしまった白昼夢は
It's over, the daydream whose curtain has been cut
ただただ 虚しさ達を 暈してみせた
Just blurring the emptinesses
思い出してしまう 夕焼ける空
I end up remembering, the sunset sky
滲むメロディ
The blurring melody
「帰ろう、道を間違わないように」
"Let's go home, so as not to lose our way"
アディショナルメモリー
Additional Memory
逆さまになって ぎゅっと繋いだ手を宙に浮かべて
Turned upside down, I let go of our tightly clasped hands into the air
泣いてしまって 買ってしまって 贅沢な走馬灯
I ended up crying, ended up buying into a luxurious kaleidoscope of memories
夕風の向こうに 恋を認めたためて 火を灯す
Beyond the evening breeze, I admit my love and light a fire
過ぎ去ってゆく 腐ってゆく 溶かした本音は
Passing by, rotting away, my melted true feelings
存在証明を 拒んでしまったストーリー
A story that rejected its own proof of existence
「私なんてさ」言いたくなかったな
I didn't want to say, "Someone like me..."
拭えない涙も 言葉も嘘も
The tears I can't wipe away, the words, the lies
友達なんかに なりたくなかったな
I never wanted us to just be friends
きっと届かないよな ごめんね 大好きだよ
It surely won't reach you, will it? I'm sorry, I love you
これが勘違いなら 知りたくなかったな
If this is all a misunderstanding, I didn't want to know
溢れ出す涙が 空に吸い込まれる
My overflowing tears are swallowed up by the sky
もう戻れないのに もう帰れないのに
Even though I can't go back, even though I can't return
今更疼くんだよ 逆さまになったまま
It's aching now, remaining upside down
散っていった 散っていった 散っていった走馬灯
Scattered, scattered, the scattered kaleidoscope of memories
夕映えの向こう 想いを染め上げた 後悔の詩
Beyond the sunset, a poem of regret dyed with my feelings
消さないでいて 覚えていて 残した本音は
Don't erase it, please remember my left-behind true feelings
幸せを拒んでしまったストーリー
A story that ended up rejecting happiness
友達なんかで 終わりたくなかったな
I didn't want it to end with us just being friends
届かない涙が 空に吸い込まれる
My unreaching tears are swallowed up by the sky
これが勘違いでも これが勘違いでも
Even if this is a misunderstanding, even if it's a mistake
ずっと言いたかったの さよなら 大好きだよ
I've always wanted to say: Goodbye, I love you
感電 作詞・作曲：米津玄師
Kanden | Lyrics/Composer: Kenshi Yonezu
逃げ出した夜の往来 行方は未だ不明
Traffic in the night I ran away into; destination still unknown
回り回って虚しくって 困っちゃったワンワンワン
Going round and round, it's so empty, I'm at a loss, woof woof woof
失ったつもりもないのに 何か足りない気分
I don't think I've lost anything, yet I feel like something's missing
ちょっと変にハイになって 吹かし込んだ四輪車
Getting a bit strangely high, revving up my four-wheeled car
兄弟よ 如何しよう もう何も考えない様
Brother, what should we do? Let's try not to think about anything
銀河系の外れへと さよなら
Saying goodbye as we head to the edge of the galaxy
真実も道徳も 動作しないイカれた夜でも
Even on a crazy night where truth and morality don't function
僕ら手を叩いて笑いあう
We'll clap our hands and laugh together
ダダダダ シラネーナンダカンダ
Da da da da, I don't know, this and that
たった一瞬のこの煌めきを
This brilliance of just a single moment
食べ尽くそう二人で くだばるまで
Let's the two of us devour it all until we drop dead
そして幸運を 僕らに祈りを
And then, pray for good luck for us
まだ行こう 誰も追いつけないくらいのスピードで
Let's keep going, at a speed that nobody can catch up to
稲妻のように生きていたいだけ
I just want to live like a bolt of lightning
お前はどうしたい？返事はいらない
What do you want to do? I don't need an answer
転がした車窓と情景 動きは未だ不明
The scenery passing by the car window; movement is still unknown
邪魔くさくって色付いた 迷い込んだニャンニャンニャン
It's annoying and colorful, wandered in, meow meow meow
追い立てて落とした財布 誰か見ませんでしたか
The wallet I dropped while being chased; has anyone seen it?
馬鹿みたいに付いてないね 茶化してよはいはいした
I'm stupidly out of luck, aren't I? Make fun of me, yeah yeah I did it
予報をもう一丁 漫画みたいな喧嘩しようぜ
One more forecast; let's have a fight like something out of a manga
...かわせて おためしで
...try exchanging them
ゼロとボロの 分類さえできない 街を
In a city where you can't even tell the difference between zero and junk
抜け出したって 互いに笑い合う
Even if we escape, we'll laugh together
メロウなエンディング
A mellow ending
それは鼓動 切なさを鳴らすもの
That's a heartbeat, something that rings out sadness
追いかけた途端に 見失っちゃうの
The moment I chase it, I lose sight of it
きっと永遠が どっかにあるんだと
Surely eternity is out there somewhere
明後日を 探し回るのも 悪くはないでしょう
Searching for the day after tomorrow isn't so bad, right?
思い出が どっかに消えた朝より
Rather than a morning where memories have vanished somewhere
こんな夜の方が まだマシさ
A night like this is much better
肺に睡蓮 遠くのサイレン
Water lilies in my lungs, a distant siren
響き合う境界線
Resonating boundaries
愛し合う様に 喧嘩しようぜ
Let's fight as if we love each other
遣る瀬無さ 引っ下げて
Carrying this helplessness with us
肺に睡蓮 遠くのサイレン
Water lilies in my lungs, a distant siren
響き合う境界線
Resonating boundaries
愛し合う様に 喧嘩しようぜ
Let's fight as if we love each other
遣る瀬無さ 引っ下げて
Carrying this helplessness with us
たった一瞬の この煌めきを
This radiance of just a single moment
食べ尽くそう 二人でくたばるまで
Let's devour it until we both drop dead
そして鼓動 僕らにノリを
And may the heartbeat give us a rhythm
まだ行こう 誰も追いつけないくらいのスピードで
Let's keep going, at a speed no one can catch up to
それは鼓動 切なさを鳴らすもの
That's a heartbeat, something that rings out sadness
追いかけた途端に 見失っちゃうの
The moment I chase it, I lose sight of it
きっと永遠が どっかにあるんだと
Surely eternity is out there somewhere
明後日を 探し回るのも 悪くはないでしょう
Searching for the day after tomorrow isn't so bad, right?
稲妻の様に 生きてたいだけ
I just want to live like a bolt of lightning
お前はどうした 返事はいらない
What about you? I don't need an answer
みんな行くよー！
Everyone, let's go!
破滅の純情
作詞：西直紀 / 作曲：コモリタミノル
Pure Heart of Destruction
Lyrics: Naoki Nishi / Composition: Minoru Komorita
燃え上がるガレキの上に立っている
Standing atop the burning rubble
いつからか 何故なのか 忘れたけど
I've forgotten since when or why
息継ぎもできない 炎の中では
Inside the flames where I can't even catch my breath
探しても 見つけても 意味がないよ
There's no point in searching or finding
壊せ 超えろ 過去のエクスタシー
Destroy and transcend the ecstasy of the past
たとえ最悪でも 未来を選べ
Even if it's the worst, choose the future
行くよ！
Here we go!
ギリギリまで Love Forever
Until the very limit, Love Forever
悶えるほど 歌えば
If you sing until you writhe
魂は どろまみれ
Your soul will be covered in mud
それでもまだ 叫べば
If you still keep on screaming
生きることに 滾れば
If you seethe with the will to live
その先は 破滅の純情
Beyond that is the pure heart of destruction
生き抜ける狂気を胸に走ってる
Running with the madness to survive in my heart
いつまでか 何故なのか 知らないけど
I don't know until when or why
瞬きもできない 速度の中では
Inside the speed where I can't even blink
喚いても 嘆いても 虚しいだけ
It's just empty, no matter how much you cry out or grieve
唸れ 弾け ヒトのエモーション
Roar and burst, human emotion
たとえ最低でも 自分を選べ
Even if it's the lowest, choose yourself
飛ぶよ！
We're flying!
ズタズタまで Love Forever
Until you're in tatters, Love Forever
震えるほど 踊れば
If you dance until you tremble
魂は むつぶれだし
Your soul begins to crumble
それでもまだ 動けば
If you still keep on moving
光る空に 届けば
If you reach the shining sky
その先は 破滅の純情
Beyond that is the pure heart of destruction
純情
Pure heart
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
声出して声出してー！
Let's hear your voices!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
踊れ、歌え、次のサバイバル
Dance, sing, the next survival
守る覚悟でなら地獄を進め
If you're prepared to protect, proceed through hell
好きよ
I love you
何回目のラストエバー
How many times has it been 'last ever'?
すべてあなた失くせば魂は
If I lose everything to you, my soul will...
乱舞のたち　イェーイ！
Be a sword in a wild dance, yay!
生まれる日に戻れば　消え去る日に眠れば
If I return to the day of birth, if I sleep on the day of fading
その先は　微熱の戦場
Beyond that is a battlefield of slight fever
ギリギリまでラストフォーエバー
Until the very limit, last forever
悶えるほど歌えば魂は
If I sing until I writhe, my soul will...
輪廻に咲き　イェーイ！
Bloom in reincarnation, yay!
それでもまだ叫べば　生きることに滾れば
If I still shout, if I seethe with living
その先は　破滅の純情
Beyond that is the pure heart of destruction
ああ　たまらないの、ベイビー
Ah, I can't stand it, baby
許してあげるわ
I will forgive you
カオスの純情
Pure heart of chaos
イェーイ！
Yay!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our fresh heart-throbs resound
キラメキライダー☆
作詞：辻 純更 / 作曲・編曲：石濱 翔（MONACA）
Kirameki Rider☆
Lyrics: Sumiyo Tsuji / Composition & Arrangement: Sho Ishihama (MONACA)
最高の時間最高の仲間と
The best time with the best friends
きらめきに乗って　イェーイ！
Riding on the sparkle, yay!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
覚えてるかな、最初の歌
Do you remember the first song?
私　声が震えていたんだ　少し
My voice was trembling a little bit
あの日から続く未来は
The future that continues from that day
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
Is the today we grasped together
もっともっともっともっと　加速するハート
More, more, more, more, an accelerating heart
一緒に行くよどこまでも
I'll go anywhere with you
Are you ready? OK!
開け、夢の扉を
Open the door to dreams
1, 2, 3! キラメキライダー
1, 2, 3! Kirameki Rider
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう　最高の時間最高の仲間と
Let's make our fresh heart-throbs resound
The best time with the best friends
ここにいるよ、見つけてくれたから
I'm right here, because you found me
君に会いたくてやって来たんだ　みんなで歌おう
I came here because I wanted to see you
Let's all sing together
終わらないメロディ
An unending melody
きらめきを纏って　イェーイ！
Wearing the sparkle, yay!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
届いてるかな、私の声
Is my voice reaching you?
届けたいのは、君に笑顔
What I want to deliver to you is a smile
理想の高さに　悔しくて
The height of ideals made me frustrated
みんなと泣いた夜もあったね
There were nights I cried with everyone, weren't there?
もっともっともっともっと　加速するハート
More, more, more, more, an accelerating heart
一緒に行くよどこまでも
I'll go anywhere with you
Are you ready? OK!
進め、希望の道を
Move forward on the road of hope
1, 2, 3! キラメキライダー
1, 2, 3! Kirameki Rider
真っ直ぐな気持ちカラフルに奏でたいんだ　最高の場所最高の皆んなと
I want to play my straightforward feelings colorfully
At the best place with the best people
ここにいるよ、幻なんかじゃない
I'm right here, it's not a phantom
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart may be dyed in happiness
重なり合ってハーモニー
Overlapping together, harmony
きらめきを纏って
Wearing the sparkle
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep singing
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep dancing
今をわがままもいいでしょ
Is it okay to be selfish for now?
だって楽しすぎて戻れない
Because it's so much fun, I can't go back
輝くステージでもっともっと
On this shining stage, more and more...
お願いずっと
...please, forever!
僕が主役でもいいですか？
Is it okay if I'm the lead?
イェーイ！おめでとう！
Yay! Congratulations!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
みんなのおかげで1年、1周年を迎えられました！
本当にありがとう！
Thanks to everyone, I've reached my 1st anniversary!
Thank you so much!
大好きな先輩たちです！
They're my beloved seniors!
イェーイ！
Yay!
嬉しい、楽しい、愛しいだけじゃ語れない
Happy, fun, dear—those words aren't enough
今も今も悩みはあるけど
Even now, I still have worries, but...
ここにいるよ私 ここにいるよ
I am here, I am right here
君と同じ世界を見つめて
Staring at the same world as you
いくよ！キラメキライダー！
Here we go! Kirameki Rider!
生まれたての鼓動を響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats resonate
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best time with the best friends
ここにいるよ見つけてくれたから
I am here because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
みんなで歌おう
I came here because I wanted to see you
Let's all sing together
終わらないメロディー
An endless melody
煌めきまとって 煌めきまとって
Clad in sparkle, clad in sparkle
イェーイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Yay! High! High! High!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
High! High! High! High!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
楽しかったー！楽しかったー！
That was fun! So much fun!
あのもう大好きで尊敬している
大好きな大好きな…
I really love and respect you all...
My beloved, beloved...
照れるなー
You're making me blush.
先輩たちに来ていただきました！
宝鐘マリン先輩、星街すいせい先輩、そしてるしあ先輩！
...seniors came to join me!
Houshou Marine-senpai, Hoshimachi Suisei-senpai, and Rushia-senpai!
るしあ先輩に来ていただきました！
本当に豪華なステージ、ありがとう！
Rushia-senpai came too!
Thank you for such a gorgeous stage!
ありがとう！いつもありがとうね！
大好き！
Thank you! Thank you as always!
I love you guys!
イェーイ！ずっとずっと大好き！
ありがとう、本当に！
Yay! I'll always love you!
Thank you, really!
あの、みんな本当に忙しい中集まってくれて、
今回ね、延期ということで最初の…
Everyone gathered even though they're busy.
Since this was postponed, on the original date...
最初の月ももちろん来てくれて、
本当に時間を作ってくれました！
...they came for me then too,
really making time for me!
みんな本当にありがとう！
Thank you all so much!
また先輩たちと一緒にステージで歌えるように、
4期生も頑張りながら…
I'll do my best as a 4th gen member so I can
sing on stage with my seniors again...
頑張ります！ありがとうございました！
I'll do my best! Thank you very much!
時間がね、もうね、やばいということで、
Time is, well, running out, so...
めちゃめちゃ名残惜しいけど、帰りたくない！
It's so hard to say goodbye, I don't want to leave!
帰りたくないよー！ここにいちゃうよー！
I don't want to go! I'm staying right here!
お前ら帰るぞ！行くよ！
We're going home, you guys! Let's go!
ありがとう！おめでとうかなた！
Thank you! Congratulations, Kanata!
またねー！ありがとう！おめでとう！
See you! Thank you! Congratulations!
またねー！
See ya!
ということでね、素敵な先輩たちとも一緒に
歌わせていただくことができました！
And so, I was able to sing together with
such wonderful seniors!
みんなのおかげです。ありがとうございます！
It's all thanks to everyone. Thank you so much!
ここでなんと！1周年記念といえば！
ドゥルドゥルドゥルドゥル…ドン！
And now! Speaking of the 1st anniversary...
*Drumroll* ...Boom!
出たー！活動一周年記念ボイス 天音かなた！
There it is! Amane Kanata 1st Anniversary Memorial Voice!
天音かなた 活動一周年記念ボイス
Amane Kanata 1st Anniversary Memorial Voice
本日発売開始！21時45分からだ、もう開始されていますね！
On sale today! From 9:45 PM—it's already started!
こちらBOOTHで発売されております！
今回はね、記念ボイスとともにグッズも2種類！
This is on sale at BOOTH!
This time, there are two types of goods along with the voice!
おしお先生のね、見てこの素敵なタペストリー！
おしおママにかなたの泣き顔を描いてもらいました！
Look at this wonderful tapestry by Oshio-sensei!
I had Oshio-mama draw Kanata's crying face!
これ以外にはね、おしおママが出してくれた本の中で…
Besides this, in the book Oshio-mama released...
そして、みんな覚えてる？5月とか6月くらいにさ、
「手裏剣のネックレスがほしい」って言ってたでしょ？
And, does everyone remember? Around May or June,
you all said you wanted a shuriken necklace, right?
それを今回叶えました！ドーン！
I've made that a reality this time! Boom!
全部セット特典はですね、箔押し複製サイン入りの…
The complete set bonus is a foil-stamped replica signature...
しかもちょっとさっきの泣いているお顔から
ちょっとはにかんで笑っているというね！
...and it's a bit of a shy smile,
different from that crying face earlier!
なのかなという感じです。
...is what I guess it's like.
こちらね、全部セットの特典でございます。全部セット。
This is the bonus for the full set. The full set.
そしてですね、みんな気になっているであろうね、手裏剣じゃないですけど、
And then, as for what everyone is probably curious about, it's not a shuriken, but...
天使の輪っかのアクセサリー。みんなとね約束したので、
the angel's halo accessory. I promised everyone,
今回ね、ちょっと無理を言って出してもらいました！
so this time, I asked them to make it happen, even if it was a bit much!
ドどん！
Ta-da!
こちらです！ネックレス＆タッセルチャーム。
Here it is! Necklace & Tassel Charm.
えっとね、これチャームだけでも確かね、あの買えるはずなので、
Um, I believe you can buy just the charm too,
あの僕はね、あの僕がオタクだったら、うーん、
so if it were me, if I were a fan, um,
ネックレスは買えないけど、でもちょっとした手裏剣が欲しいと思った時にね、
I might not be able to buy the necklace, but if I wanted a little shuriken,
あの買えるようなものも欲しいなと思ってチャームも用意しました。みんなつけてくれる？
I wanted something affordable too, so I prepared a charm. Will everyone wear it?
鞄とかさ。しかもね、ゴールドとシルバーでね、ちゃんとね。これどっちがいいかなって悩んだんだけど、
On your bags and stuff. Also, it comes in both gold and silver. I was torn on which one would be better,
やっぱ人によって似合うの違うからさ、両方作ってもらいました。
but since different things look good on different people, I had them make both.
めちゃめちゃ無理を言って。ありがとうございます、本当に。
I really pushed for it. Thank you so much, seriously.
よし、そして、ドどん！
Alright, and next, ta-da!
あ、ドどん。
Ah, ta-da.
はい、こちらがですね、あのグッズとして付いてくるタペストリーでございます。
Yes, here is the tapestry that comes with the goods.
いや〜もうさ、僕のタペストリー全部持っているっていう人はさ、もう部屋中かなたになってんじゃない？
Wow... I mean, people who have all my tapestries, isn't your room just full of Kanata by now?
僕もサンプルでね、あのグッズいつも頂いているんですけど、それをね、全部ココの部屋にね、
I always receive samples of the goods, and I give them all to Coco for her room,
あのあげてるから、ココの部屋がちょっと平民の部屋みたいになってるんだけどさ。
so Coco's room is starting to look like a fan's room.
あの今回のこれもね、あの飾るので、そうするとね、
I'll be displaying this one too, which means...
あの間接的に桐生ココとお揃いということに皆さんなりますので、
you'll all indirectly be matching with Kiryu Coco.
ぜひぜひこちらの、おしお先生の素敵なイラスト飾ってください。という感じで、
So please, please display this lovely illustration by Oshio-sensei. And with that,
という感じでオッケーかな？はい。これでオッケーですね。
is that all? Yes. That's it.
えーと、ではですね、えーと、あと、もうこれラストスパート、
Um, well then, um, we're in the final stretch now,
あと2曲になりました。
with only two songs left.
みんなへのね、気持ちをいっぱい込めて歌いたいと思います。
I want to sing with all my feelings for everyone.
えー、それでは、あ、マイクもね、後で頂いてと。
Well then, oh, I'll get my mic later too.
それでは、最後の曲、聴いてください。『炎』。
And now, please listen to the final song: "Homura".
さよなら ありがとう 声の限り
Goodbye, thank you, with all my voice
悲しみよりもっと大事なこと
Something more important than sadness
去りゆく背中に 伝えたい
I want to tell your departing back
ぬくもりと痛みに 間に合うように
So I can make it in time with warmth and pain
このまま続くと思っていた
I thought it would continue like this
僕らの明日を描いていた
I was drawing our tomorrow
呼び合っていた 光がまだ
The light that was calling out to each other still...
胸の奥に熱いのに
...is hot deep in my chest
僕たちは燃え盛る 旅の途中で出会い
We met in the middle of a blazing journey
手を取りそして離した 未来のために
Took hands and then let go, for the sake of the future
夢が一つ叶うたび 僕は君を想うだろう
Every time a dream comes true, I will probably think of you
強くなりたいと願い 泣いた
I wished to become strong and cried
決意を 餞に
My determination as a parting gift
懐かしい思いに 囚われたり
Being trapped in nostalgic feelings
残酷な世界に 泣き叫んで
Crying out in this cruel world
大人になるほど 増えて行く
The more I become an adult, the more they increase
もう何一つだって 失いたくない
I don't want to lose even one more thing
悲しみに呑まれ 落ちてしまえば
If I am swallowed by sadness and fall
痛みを感じなくなるけれど
I won't feel pain anymore, but...
君の言葉 君の願い
...your words, your wish...
僕は守り抜くと 誓ったんだ
...I swore that I would protect them to the end
音を立てて 崩れ落ちて行く
Noisily crumbling away
音を立てて 崩れ落ちてゆく
With a roar, it all comes crumbling down
一つだけの かけがえのない世界
This one and only, irreplaceable world
手を伸ばし 抱き止めた 激しい光の束
I reached out and held tight to a fierce bundle of light
輝いて消えてった 未来のために
It shone and then vanished, for the sake of the future
託された幸せと 約束を越えて行く
I'll go beyond the happiness entrusted to me and the promise we made
振り返らずに進むから
Because I will move forward without looking back
前だけ向いて叫ぶから
Because I will look only ahead and scream
心に炎を灯して
With a flame lit in my heart
遠い未来まで……
To the distant future...
強くなれる理由を知った
I've found the reason to be strong
僕を連れて進め
Take me with you and move forward
紅蓮華
作詞：LiSA 作曲：草野華余子
Gurenge
Lyrics: LiSA  Composition: Kayoko Kusano
泥だらけの走馬灯に酔う
Drunk on a mud-covered revolving lantern of memories
こわばる心 震える手は
My heart stiffens, my hands tremble
掴みたいものがある それだけさ
There's something I want to grasp, that's all
夜の匂いに空睨んでも
Even if I glare at the sky in the scent of the night
変わっていけるのは自分自身だけ それだけさ
The only thing that can change is myself, that's all
強くなれる理由を知った
I've found the reason to be strong
僕を連れて進め
Take me with you and move forward
どうしたって！消せない夢も 止まれない今も
No matter what! A dream that won't fade, a present that won't stop
誰かのために強くなれるなら
If I can become strong for someone's sake
ありがとう 悲しみよ
Thank you, sadness
世界に打ちのめされて 負ける意味を知った
Beaten down by the world, I learned the meaning of defeat
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ！ 運命を照らして
Gurenge, bloom in full! Shine on my destiny
イナビカリの雑音が耳を刺す
The noise of the lightning strikes pierces my ears
戸惑う心 優しいだけじゃ守れないものがある？ わかってるけど
My bewildered heart, are there things I can't protect just by being kind? I know that, but...
水面下で絡まる善悪
Good and evil tangled below the surface
透けて見える偽善に天罰
Divine punishment for the hypocrisy seen through it
Tell me why, Tell me why, Tell me why, Tell me why...
I don't need you!
逸材の花より 挑み続け咲いた一輪が美しい
More than a gifted flower, the one that kept challenging to bloom is beautiful
乱暴に敷き詰められた トゲだらけの道も 本気の僕だけに現れるから 乗り越えてみせるよ
The path roughly paved with thorns appears only to the serious me, so I'll show you I can overcome it
簡単に片付けられた 守れなかった夢も
Easily dismissed, even the dreams I couldn't protect
紅蓮の心臓に根を生やし この血に宿ってる
Take root in my crimson heart, and dwell in this blood
人知れず儚い 散りゆく結末
A secret, fleeting, scattering end
無情に破れた 悲鳴の風吹く
Heartlessly torn, the wind of screams blows
誰かの笑い声 誰かの泣き声
Someone's laughter, someone's crying
誰もが幸せを願ってる
Everyone is wishing for happiness
どうしたって！消せない夢も 止まれない今も 誰かのために強くなれるなら
No matter what! A dream that won't fade, a present that won't stop, if I can become strong for someone's sake
悲しみよ
Oh, sadness...
世界に打ちのめされて
Beaten down by the world,
負ける意味を知った
I learned the meaning of defeat.
紅蓮の華よ
Oh crimson lotus flower,
咲き誇れ
Bloom in full glory,
運命を
Illuminate
照らして
destiny.
運命を照らして
Illuminate destiny.
みんなー！ありがとうございました！
Everyone! Thank you so much!
今年もよろしくお願いします！
I'll be in your care this year too!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
みんなに 出会えて 良かった。
I'm glad I met everyone.
リスナーのみんな、
To my listeners,
そして、運営のみなさん、
and the staff,
本当にたくさんの人にありがとうございました。
thank you so much to everyone.
そして、これを見てくれてる、
And to everyone watching this,
ずっと応援してくれてるみんな、
who has supported me all along...
みんな、みんなに、出会えて良かったと思っております。
I'm truly glad that I could meet all of you.
本当にありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.